sexyescortads.com 2009-12-18

# Sexy Escorts :: privacy

|   
---  
|   |  |   
---  
  
**By proceeding to the further use of this website you expressly agree to the use and disclosure of information as described in this Privacy Policy :**

  * We allow you to visit and use our websites without revealing any personal information about yourself. Your visit to this website is anonymous, unless you yourself disclosed any private information in submitted content (personal ads, forum and blog posts, gellery images etc.). We will only collect your contact information (first name, last name, phone number, email address and any other relevant information provided by you) as well as financial information (account or credit card numbers), with your permission and for the sole purpose of maintaining of you your account and processing orders. 
  * If you make a purchase from our website, you will be asked to provide your name, billing address, email and credit card information (if you have chosen credit card as payment method). We will use such information only for processing your order and to send important order specific information such as receipt, invoice or your order status information. 
  * In addition, please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online, for example on message boards, through email, or in chat areas, that information can be collected and used by others besides the place of original publication (our website). Our website cannot be responsible for any unauthorized third party use of information that you disclose online. 
  * The information you provide will not be sold, rented, leased or otherwise forwarded to any third party. However, we may occasionally release information about our visitors when release is appropriate to comply with law, to enforce our Terms of Service agreement, or to protect the rights, property or safety of users of our services, the public, or webite owners. This includes breaking of our Terms of Service by you that result in legal actions against you or us. In this case we reserve the right to disclose the appropriate information to legal authorities including but not limited to your name, email address(es), phone number(s), IP addresses used etc. 
  * In order to provide secure processing of your credit card when ordering, SSL encryption is used. Your personal information, including sensitive credit card information, is encrypted so that it is indecipherable by others as it travels across the Internet. No credit card data is stored in our database. 
  * Our site provides links to external web sites. We do not monitor or control the content of these sites or whether they collect or process your personal data. When you click on one of those links, you leave our site and enter one that we do not control and for which we cannot be responsible. We assume no liability whatsoever for any kind of material available at such sites and recommends that you review their separate privacy policies. 

**Bookmark Our Site! (Ctrl+D)** \- **Make Us Your Homepage!**  
© [Sexy Escorts](http://www.sexyescortads.com/help/email_form/), 2002-2009
